[
  {
    "type": "Music",
    "name": "Music",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which of these artists was the first to win a Grammy?",
        "options": [
          "Billie Eilish",
          "My Chemical Romance",
          "Green Day",
          "Michael Jackson"
        ],
        "answer": "Michael Jackson"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many basic musical notes are there?",
        "options": ["One", "Four", "Seven", "Nine"],
        "answer": "Seven"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which was the first song of Coldplay?",
        "options": [
          "Ode to deodorant",
          "Viva la vida",
          "Clocks",
          "Adventure of a Lifetime"
        ],
        "answer": "Ode to deodorant"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the name of the principal singer of the band Red Hot Chili Peppers?",
        "options": [
          "Chacho Ramos",
          "Anthony Kiedis",
          "Dave Navarro",
          "Emiliano Laino"
        ],
        "answer": "Anthony Kiedis"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "LoL",
    "name": "League of Legends",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which video game company developed the game League of Legends?",
        "options": ["Activision", "Ubisoft", "Riot Games", "Capcom"],
        "answer": "Riot Games"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many lanes are there in the Summoner's Rift map of the game League of Legends?",
        "options": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
        "answer": "Three"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which tribe does League of Legends champion Leona belong to?",
        "options": ["Noxus", "Demacia", "Freljord", "Solari"],
        "answer": "Solari"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many original champions did the game League of Legends have when it was released in 2009?",
        "options": ["10", "25", "30", "40"],
        "answer": "40"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "Series",
    "name": "Series",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is the longest serie ever?",
        "options": [
          "Gunsmoke",
          "Law & Order: Special Victims Unit",
          "The Simpsons",
          "Family Guy"
        ],
        "answer": "The Simpsons"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the longest anime ever?",
        "options": ["Sazae-San", "Doraemon", "One Piece", "Naruto"],
        "answer": "Sazae-San"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the smallest child of the simpsons family?",
        "options": ["Lisa", "Bart", "Marge", "Maggie"],
        "answer": "Maggie"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which character in Futurama has only one eye?",
        "options": ["Fry", "Leela", "Nibler", "Doctor Zoidberg"],
        "answer": "Leela"
      }
    ]
  }
]
